node_modules
This might be
harder than I thought…
node_modules
MB
.
Mari, how many times do I have to tell you
to clean up your Git bran—?
node_modules
Mari…
What’s all this?
jQuery
I don’t think you need all these libraries.
Really?
node_modules
jQuery
They’re full of features! They’re so useful!
What’s this?
Bluebird.
And this?
Lodash!
Bluebird
Lodash
Ramda.
Ramda
Moment.js.
I
Moment.js
left-pad.
left-pad
Handlebars.
I
Moment.js
Handlebars
Axios with a bunch of plugins.
I
Moment.js
Handlebars
Bluebird
Axios
It took me forever to find these!
The language has a lot of these built-in, you know!
Just use those.
I know, but still…
node_modules
That should do it, I think.
So light!
node_modules
You should consult
with Shirase, too.
They might already have solutions
for what you need.
But do you really think
this’ll be good enough?
node_modules
Real people are gonna use this, you know!
Sis… are you sure
you can handle this?
It’s just…
AQ-621
Temperature
dashboard
AQ-672
Antarctic route tracker
Those tickets don’t even
give us a list of packages to use…
jQuery
Because this is a professional environment.
You need to be responsible.
jQuery
Me, responsible?
Being a professional is hard, huh?
jQuery