We’re doing a rap about coding and failing!
We’re coding, coding, failing and coding!
What’s an error that’s got you groaning?
Who, me? Well, it’s plain to see.
I got a segfault: off by one in C!
We know that one! It ain’t much fun!
We’re coding, coding, failing and coding!
What’s an error that’s got you groaning?
Me? Um… Uh…
I fixed a bug, but it was still there.
Turns out I forgot to rebuild!
What’s an error that’s got you groaning?
Um… Uh…
I accidentally pulled the plug
on my server with 425 days uptime!
I said it!
Oh boy, that’s the second time, isn’t it?
Leave it to Debian to be up for that long.
What’s an error that’s got you groaning?
Oh, not me… Let’s see.
Before I came for training,
I got an offer from a big tech company,
but I left without giving an answer.
You never mentioned this before!
Where? Where was it?!
Give them your answer now!
Yeah, yeah!
Now, now! Let’s do it now!
So, I sent an email and got a response.
What’s their reply? Don’t leave us high and dry!
They said, “Sorry. This position is no longer available.”
S-Sorry.
We’re the ones who made an error this time.
We’re coding, coding, failing and coding!